I'ma give you a bite of the sweetest thing
Baby I'm the sweetest, pussy is the meanest
Hot girl shit but I'm cold every season
No he got that pipe let him bust it till it's leak
Booty like a pillow he could use it while he's sleeping
Look don't be going through my phone cause that's the old me
Ain't the only one tryna be my one and only
Real thick moving slow that body like codeine
He a player but for Megan he cutting the whole team
That body looking nice
I got cake and I know he wanna slice
I wish a nigga would try to put me on ice
I ain't never had to chase dick in my life
I want that nasty that freaky stuff
Under my bed and keep hype up
That hand selling girl don't let him eat me up
Uh uh uh uh uh
Ooh that's the ride of your life
Hold on cause baby I might
I might just give you a bite of
The sweetest pie
Ooh baby we can go fast
I'll drive and you just lay back
I got the flavor the last
Yeah the sweetest pie
I might take you home with us
I might give you all of it
Come get your clothes up
That's the ride of your life Hold on cause baby I might